(Penny:)Oh, he does. He so does.
What should he do?
(Psychic:)He should give himself
to this relationship.
(Psychic:)Once he does, all his other pursuits
will come into focus.
(Penny:)Sheldon, do you hear that? I mean,
Amy is the key to your happiness.
(Psychic:)Exactly.
Personally and professionally.
(Psychic:)Everything will fall into place
once you commit to her.
(Sheldon:)You know what this is?
(Sheldon:)Yeah, and I reserve this word
for those rare instances
(Sheldon:)when it's truly deserved.
This is malarkey!
(Penny:)Wow, you really struck a nerve.
(Penny:)I've never heard him use
the "M" word before.
(Penny:)Here we go.
House of a 1000 Corpses.
(Emily:)Now, just so you know,
I was a nanny for three years,